Johnatan Alexander Carillo

Operations Manager

+1 202 555 5555 help@enhancv.com linkedin.com/in/johnatanc Austin,TX

SUMMARY

I am experience manager who enjoys tackling big challenges in fulfillment, manufacturing and customer service. I take pride in my ability to build high performing and engaged teams with a passion to win. Manufacturing & logistics are in my blood. For almost a decade I have been at the forefront of many manufacturing transformations as an ambitious operations leader, Lean Six Sigma strategist and functional operator.

EXPERIENCE

Operations Manager Austin, TX

Ledner Group 2017 - Ongoing

- Accountable for 3.5M monthly units at a \$12M yearly revenue.
- Led teams of 50+ permanent and agency staff, both operations and administrations.
- · Manage a portfolio of \$5M+ of campaigns in booked revenue per Quarter across NSW and QLD clients.

Area Manager

Bernier

Austin, TX

2013 - 2017

- · Led and developed a team of 80-100 Amazon Associates in the largest North American Fulfilment Centre to meet daily rate goals.
- Responsible for communicating policies to Associates and acting as the primary information source for 4 teams.
- · Partnered with other leadership to ensure the business is operating a balanced lean shift while meeting objectives.
- Achieved the 2nd highest saving for 2016 at 35.1M units.
- · Supported and upheld compliance to all safety programs to ensure a safe work environment for all associates.

Logistics Administrator
Lessard

Austin, TX
2011 - 2013

- Collaborated with beneficiary centers to project demand and prepare outgoing food pallets across 9 teams at \$1.5M operational cost.
- · Responsible for logging incoming and outgoing food donations into inventory database within the Logistics department.
- Partnered with local businesses to initiate food donations as well as maintained relationships with current donors.

ACHIEVEMENTS

33% YoY improvement in department productivity
Drove team to achieve the best direct rates in the building's history. Second best in the Amazon Robotics network.

Record high department quality benchmark

Maintained compliance and consistency to drive lowest

DPMO in building's history. Number one in Amazon Robotics

network during peak season.

PROJECTS

L/A Accessions Process Improvement

Acted as lead in agency-wide team to analyze work processes, develop standard operating procedures, build tracking database, and train more than 50 HR specialists and administrative officers on its use.

Optimizing Value Added Consortium

Research Technician for the Global Supply Chain Laboratory of Texas A&M University as part of the Talent Incubator Program. Researched, designed, and developed operational solutions within the field of supply chain management across different industries and companies.

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Bilingual) English (Bilingual) Italian (Beginner)

EDUCATION

BS in Business Administration

Austin, TX
University of Texas
2007 - 2011

www.enhancv.com Powered by 🔾 Enhancv